

Haifa, Israel

☑ dariamartvel@gmail.com | 🛅 dariamartvel

# **Summary**

3+ years experience in the field of FinTech/Banking. Current Business Analyst at Mobile Banking Company VTB. Highly experienced in working directly with end users and business owners. Acted as a liaison between business and technology teams. Specializing in business requirements development, Use Case Analysis, User Story development. Interested in implementing best solutions and making users' life better.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Business analyst & Customer Journey Expert**

Mar. 2021 - currently

INNOTECH (VTB MOBILE BANK PROJECT)

- Collect and develop business requirements documents using UML and BPMN approach.
- Create User Stories, Use Cases, process flows.
- Conduct features research for developing appropriate UI/UX.
- · Process and analyze the data obtained from the results of user interaction with the product, compile reports with the main indicators of the product, according to the calculated values, offer the team features for subsequent implementation.
- Construct Google Analytics markup for the subsequent construction of funnels and its analysis.
- Work closely with the PM and QA team to make sure all the requirements are covered and tested and to check for compliance with business requirements.

Analyst Intern Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

VTB MOBILE BANK PROJECT

- Prepared and processed data for the search engine NLP model.
- Constructed and analysed feature funnels needed for checking business metrics.
- · Conducted different types of Customer Experience researches such as In-depth interviews, Unmoderated remote usability tests, A/B tests.
- Developed Customer Journey Maps for 3 different mobile bank features.

#### **Engineer-programmer** Sept. 2019 - Mar. 2021

ROSKOSMOS STATE SPACE CORPORATE

- · Created a on-board equipment model of high-frequency radio lines for the spacecraft using C++.
- Wrote Bachelor's thesis "Telemetry Data Approximation" based on developed model.

#### Education

### MIPT(Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology)

M.S. in Applied Maths and Physics

DEPARTMENT OF APPLIED MATHEMATICS AND INFORMATICS

Sept. 2020 - Jul. 2022

• Did a Master's Thesis on NLP: "Application of Natural Language Processing in Project Management Efficiency Improvement".

#### **International Banking Institute**

DEPARTMENT OF FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT

Sept. 2020 - Jul. 2022

• Completed a professional training program in Project Management and Finance.

## MIPT(Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology)

B.S. in Applied Maths and Physics

DEPARTMENT OF AEROPHYSICS AND SPACE TECHNOLOGIES

Sept. 2016 - Jul. 2020

 Did a Bachelor's Thesis on Space Engineering: "Telemetry Parameters Approximation Technology Development for Space Vehicles and Upper Stages".

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

**SCRUM-master** Jul. 2021 - Mar. 2022

INNOTECH (VTB MOBILE BANK PROJECT)

- · Facilitated Agile ceremonies.
- Helped to optimize workflows as a SCRUM-master of a 12 members team.
- Consulted team members on working with Jira dashboards.
- · Worked on planning and backlog prioritising with PO.

DARIA MARTVEL · RÉSUMÉ